Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing That
surely someday we just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
Yep, sure looks like a warship.
So, the navy's on the
island? What? Are you sure?
When did they get here? Hey, look!
We've got company!
Wait, I know him! Hey! Hello?
What you doing here?
You remember me, don't you?
You helped me out that one time!
Straw Hat.
He's here?
That's the guy we met at
the human shop in Sabaody.
Trafalgar Law, but why is he here?
Right! Traffy!
He helped me out!
You guys know, back in the
Battle of Marine Corps,
he got me off the field and treated
my wounds. He did? Yeah, sure.
He saved my life like Jinbei.
Okay, I'm gonna go talk
to him right now. Hey!
I didn't expect to run into you.
Small world, huh?
You saved me.
I owe you one. Really.
Vix!
Hey, wait, uh, where'd your buddies go?
Quick, hand over Straw Hat.
Hand him over and we can escape.
He'll die without my help.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
Where's my brother?
What will happen to him if he
remains in that state? Simple.
If he keeps flailing around, the
more likely he is to open his wound.
And if that happens,
chances are he'll die.
He needs to rest, for two weeks at least.
Got it, or he won't heal.
I understand, and thank
you for everything.
Hmm.
It looks like you pulled
through, Straw Hat.
Well, glad my treatment took, but
you don't have to thank me for it.
I did it on a whim, that's all.
We're not buddies.
Don't forget, we're both pirates.
I know.
Opponents, rivals, enemies.
But enemy or not, you
still help me. So thanks.
This is cool.
First Team Bay and now you.
I'm getting a lot of thank
yous checked off my list.
Hey, over there, on the ground, a Marine!
Is that who I think it is?
Can I get a little help here, Trafalgar?
Hey!
Wait! Please!
Oh, no.
Smoker!
Smoking!
Marines!
Wait, that girl! I know her!
Luffy, we got Marines headed our way! Yep!
What do you see? What happened?
You think smoking's alright?
Please wake up!
That's what I thought!
It's Smokey and his crew!
Long time no see!
There's a hole in his chest.
Smoker, no!
In order to become a member
of the Seven Warlords,
he delivered the hearts of a hundred
pirates to the Navy Headquarters.
He's off the rails!
Damn you,
damn you,
damn you, damn you,
damn you, come on, really,
I hate this kind of thing, too much drama,
room,
Shambles.
Ah, damn, he took her down again.
Smokey isn't moving either.
Are they both dead?
Once wasn't enough.
Please, I win again, Captain.
Loopy!
That's our cue to get out of here!
Hold on. Hey, you! Traffy!
Got a question for you.
Head over to the lab, around the back.
When you get there, you'll
find what you're looking for.
We'll meet again soon.
We both have things we mean to get back.
He met me.
He's going to save me from this indignity.
I'm a former pirate, not a horse.
Let's get as far away from
those Navy Pucks as we can.
Think Smokey's going to be okay?
That looked rough.
Traffy didn't go easy on it.
Hey, look, guys, it's
Straw Hat Luffy. Fire!
Planet!
Don't worry about those guys.
Smokey's down.
The captain, too.
Who cares about the
samurai and the breads?
Not me, I say!
More importantly, where
can I find a camera?
I gotta take some pictures
before we all change back!
Pictures of what, exactly?
Then stop making my nose bleed,
or your nose, or whatever!
If we're making demands, Nami, then unbutton
my shirt so I can show off my Mechapex!
I know it's cold!
Hang in there!
We can make it!
We'll figure something out!
I liked it better when
you weren't so nice.
This is kind of creeping me out.
I don't get it.
Did someone play a trick
and make you switch bodies?
It's so cold without my fur!
You humans sure do have it rough!
You gotta stop. He needs help.
It's too cold.
I can't move.
I'm freezing.
Me too.
I'm starting to get scared.
Damn it.
We shouldn't have taken the kids with
us until we figured out where to go.
On the upside, I don't feel cold
at all with Chopper's fur on.
Well, I've got enough fur
for a couple of coats.
No way!
That's my body!
Okay, fine, but I don't think we're gonna
find any warm clothing just lying around
Maybe there's a lodge or something.
Yeah, yeah with a mirror and a camera
And a shower would be nice
Very well, I can see we
have no other choice.
I need all of you to place a
leaf upon your heads Wait, what?
Why would we do that?
Don't joke, dude.
The poor kiddos are gonna collapse
from the cold Besides, what leaves?
There aren't any.
Just look around.
There are no plants.
Fine. Forget leaves.
Start gathering some stones instead.
Hurry.
Okay, we'll do it, but this
had better not be a prank.
I'll get them for the kids, too.
Now what?
We've got the rocks.
I hope you don't do some stupid spell
like abracadabra, make it not cold.
Because I'd kill you all right.
Poof.
You do,
you're welcome, small one.
I have not always possessed the strange
ability, but one day I ate a fruit,
an unusual one,
and since then I have been able to
disguise myself and others as I please.
I know little of foreign clothing;
I hope this will suffice also,
due to the nature of the magic.
The clothes will disappear
if you remove them.
He covered my boobs.
I didn't know you'd eaten
a Devil Fruit. What? Devil?
Hey, hold on a second.
This whole time, you had that power.
So why didn't you use it sooner?
I was helpless.
That little breastband she's wearing,
I couldn't bring myself to cover it up.
Oh! Curve?
That... really...
itches.
Jeez, say it. I'm hurt.
Admitting that isn't going to kill you.
I itch. Oh, hey!
Look who it is! Huh?
Hi, guys!
Hey! Hey! Yay!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
What are they doing here?
Bye!
Everyone okay?
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Dude, now what?
Hey, it's Luffy!
Zoro and Usopp, too! Robin!
I'm so happy to see you! What the?
Why's the jackass cook
prancing around like that?
You've called us strange things to people.
Is it just me?
Are there giant children with them, too?
Wait!
No, don't do it! Franky! Down, boy!
Out of the cold, finally.
This building reminds me
a lot of the other one.
But this one is badly damaged, as if
there were some sort of explosion here.
Long as it gets us out of that
blizzard, it's fine by me.
Now, let's talk. Who's up first?
I can't believe I did that to my own body.
Here, let me see if I can help.
What are you doing, Saatchi?
Get your hands off me!
But it's me, Chopper!
My legs are back.
I'm almost told now.
My extra legs!
I'm on a set already!
Enough!
You are never a centaur,
so just let it go!
How very odd.
Quite a funny chap, isn't he?
The skeleton...
...is talking.
Hey!
Do a trick!
Yeah, the tank thing!
Not now!
Right.
That's not him.
You sure?
You've got to be craving one. Go on.
I know you like to smoke
when you're stressed out.
So, smoke. Right.
First up, we're gonna need
to know who's who here.
Franky, got that?
Not Chopper.
You get hurt, I'm useless. Remember that.
Hey guys, Chopper speaking.
If you have any injuries, come to me.
I'm Nami, okay?
No laser beams, no tanks, don't ask.
And now I present to you...
Nami! Yeah!
Hello, beautiful!
Defile my body again, I dare you!
I'll stop, I promise!
Please don't hurt Nami
again, she's too pretty!
No, don't do it!
That would be suicide!
Touch me and you get a fine.
100,000 berries.
No, make it two.
But my dream!
Shut up!
Wouldn't be so funny
if it happened to you!
Let's start from the top and
make sure we've got it straight.
This head and legs
belong to a Wano samurai.
The distress signal we
intercepted before coming to
the island was actually meant
for the big boss crocotar.
and was sent by one of his men.
Seems our sliced-up samurai
pal did some slicing
of his own with the centaurs
on the receding end.
Yes, I fought them, but
only to rescue my son.
His name is Momonosuke.
He's missing, and those men
were in my way. Just look!
You can see with your own eyes how many
children were prisoners
in that foul facility.
I have no doubt my son is one of them.
Yeah, there were others.
More children like us.
I guess your son could be one
of them, but I don't know.
Right, but what happened
after that distress signal?
Who the heck sliced you?
The man we encountered, him!
The one with the cold eyes and the
silly cap who bears the title Warlord.
What?
Wait, Traffy?
He's a Warlord now, really? Yes.
Well, a lot can change in two years.
Bastard, he took his
blade and carved me up.
My head was kept in the facility.
My torso remained where it fell.
And my legs were chased
away by a vile beast.
They were making a
valiant effort to escape.
But they became stuck on something.
Which was the dragon.
That explains it.
Oh, right, a warlord.
You were mad at one.
I remember now.
Wait, but it was just legs?
So how did he talk?
That's a real good question.
It's simple.
By farting.
It's a talent of mine.
Here, I'll show you.
Fart talking?
Okay, gross. But useful.
Didn't smell so bad outside.
Would you believe I met another
partial person recently?
You have a head and legs.
He just had a torso.
That's Fanny.
Right, because that
was his torso, dumbass.
Oh, dear!
You saw it, skeleton? Truly?
Where is my torso?
We must go there at once!
The whole heart thing.
You doing okay without one?
I think so.
Talking to her is hard enough, but...
There was a ship hidden
beside the laboratory.
The letters CC were written on it. What?
I didn't know there was a ship?
You saw it, Vice Admiral?
Yeah,
if it was left over from the old
days before the island was destroyed,
the mark should be PH for Punk Hazard.
I'm guessing that Law
isn't the mastermind here.
Someone else is.
Someone with the initial CC.
And I think I know who.
It would make sense.
Him being here on this island.
A lot of things are
starting to fall into place.
I believe the person behind this
is a former colleague of Dr.
Vegapunk A scientist named Caesar Clown
Heavens, what have you done now, Law?
Well
If anyone's got a complaint, it's me
Caesar.
I think I have some
information that might help.
Huh?
I noticed something unusual a while back.
Suspicious reports from this area.
A lot of reports, all of them
concerning child abduction.
You mean like a kidnapping ring?
Yes.
I don't know if I can handle this, Cap!
It's like you're not you anymore!
You've got to suck it up, Marine.
We're stuck like this for now.
All right, Toshiki, get back on track.
These reports you're talking about,
why haven't I heard of them before?
Please button up, I can't
even look at myself!
There's something wrong
about seeing her like this!
I know I shouldn't like
it, but God help me, I do!
That's enough!
I have noticed that accidents at sea
happen fairly frequently in this area.
And it does seem that an unusual
number involved children.
Oh, yeah, that's true. Right? Yeah.
The thing is, per the
communication department...
Oh, right, no glasses.
Well, from what I've heard, we get
a whole lot of abduction reports.
But somehow they always end up labeled
in the newspaper as accidents at sea,
the work of pirates,
or simply a lost child.
And I guess it's possible the
incidents are reported incorrectly.
Possible.
But unfortunately to me it seems
far more likely that, well...
Are you going to finish
your sentence, Tashigi?
come on saying it out
loud won't change anything
we all know we saw a bunch
of kids on the island
earlier what you're too
afraid to say is you think
there really have been
a series of kidnappings
and you believe the perpetrator
is here on punk hazard
but if your suspicions
about that are correct
those news articles
weren't simple mistakes the
reporters were deliberately
misled because someone in g5
wanted those abduction
reports covered up hold on
is smoky saying that somebody
in our ranks is working
with the kidnapper what
the hell smokey happy for
a soldier crew like that
sure we're not the smartest
or strongest marines there
are but that doesn't change
the fact that We just tried
to be part of the maze!
Quit your bitching!
Don't hurt us!
You fools couldn't
steal candy from a baby.
You're not even worth suspecting.
What?
But don't let loyalty blind you.
Not even the Navy is immune to corruption.
At the end of the day, the
Navy is just a group of people.
And people aren't perfect.
Making assumptions is dangerous.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
Ah! Oh!
understood captain
never mind morons um guys
i'm the captain right sorry
we're still getting used to
this i could still be wrong i
don't have any proof it's a
theory that's all that doesn't
matter theory or not it's
something we need to keep in mind
Unfortunately, as it stands, my heart
and both our bodies are at law's mercy.
We're both stuck here till we settle that.
But I want a third of you to leave by
ship and report what we've found so far.
Just one problem with that, Vice Admiral.
If you remember, our
warship was destroyed.
I told you I saw a ship, didn't I?
Steal it. Oh, yeah!
I hadn't thought of that!
Stealing's bad, though!
Just do it, all right?
And be careful nobody catches you.
Meanwhile, I'm going to find a
way to get my heart and body back.
and hunt down the twisted
bastard who's behind all this.
I was finally able to get through to him.
We have permission to kill them all.
The Straw Hat Pirates, the G5
crew, Foxfire Kin'emon as well.
No matter who dies on this island,
Joker will ensure the losses are
officially listed as accidents at sea.
Catch as many of them as possible.
The more guinea pigs, the merrier.
Yes, master.
I prefer them alive, but you may kill
any that can't be taken with poison.
Where did Law go?
He left the room a few minutes ago.
Well, be careful.
These pirates have large bounties.
One is 400 million.
The others range from 50
berries to 120 million.
All are wanted, and their total
bounties are 800 million and 50 berries.
They're notorious despite the fact they've
been enacted for the past two years.
Their bounties haven't
increased in that time.
They could be more powerful
than the numbers show.
You're ever the font
of information, Monet.
Help, Master!
Huh?
You look half frozen.
Have you been wandering
around outside without a coat?
We were robbed by pirates, Master.
Master, what's worse is that the scheming
lowlights took Boss Brownbeard with them.
Please, Master, we have to help him.
Really?
How absolutely terrible.
Don't worry about Brownbeard.
I promise you we will retrieve him.
Now go on back to the room.
As it happens, you're in luck.
We've just finished a new medicine.
Exactly what you need.
It will both warm and heal you. Really?
That's so kind.
Will you help the others too?
Sure, certainly.
But first, let's get you treated.
You do so much for us, Master.
I don't know how to repay you.
Are you kidding?
What the hell is this, Usopp?
I think you're totally super, bro.
I don't care anymore.
Thanks, Usopp!
Great idea!
This thing detracts from Nami's beauty.
Ah, quit whining.
Without some sort of system like this,
we're never going to remember who's who.
It's a Brownbeard, huh?
That's right.
I'm sure you've heard that name.
It's what I used to go by.
Nope, sorry.
Are you kidding, you fool?
Something's up.
You wouldn't say a word before,
and now you won't stop yapping.
Why are you so eager
to run your mouth now?
Oh-ho.
I'm in a good mood because
you guys are in for it.
Law knows that I'm with you
now, and he's gonna come for me.
I despise all the worthless
pirates of your damn generation.
Law's the exception. Hold on.
What do you mean, our generation?
Don't you know anything, little fool?
I mean the 11 rookies
with bounties over 100
million who arrived at
Sabaody two years ago.
You lot and Blackbeard.
People call you puns the worst generation.
Troublemakers who were born
at the change of the era.
Reckless fools whose actions will
determine the future of this world.
After Whitebeard died, you all came to
the new world and began raising hell.
Anytime something big happened,
a member of your generation was
usually right in the thick of things.
Blackbeard, Kid, Law, Drake, and Hawkins.
Basil Hawkins was the one who shattered
my crew, leaving us defeated and broken.
It was because of him that
my pirate career ended.
The coward took my legs from me.
My crew was annihilated.
I was fleeing for my life
when at last I arrived here.
on the island known as Punk Hazard.
Do you fools even know
what this place is? Huh?
This island is not what it was.
It used to be a paradise
teeming with life,
home to creatures of
all shapes and colors.
Wow, for real?
It's nothing like that anymore.
This island housed a laboratory of a
government scientist known as Dr. Vegapunk.
He and his team were
stationed here with the
task of developing new
chemicals and weapons.
Vegapunk needed subjects on
which to test his inventions,
so instead of going to prison,
criminals were sent here, where
they were experimented on.
Four years ago, Vegapunk tested one of
his chemical weapons, and it went very,
very wrong.
Two of the three labs exploded,
destroyed almost entirely.
We are standing in the
remains of one right now.
That makes sense.
A huge explosion would
do this kind of damage,
so Robin's theory was right after all.
Intense heat and toxic
substances seeped into the air,
and none of the plants or
animals on the island survived.
Vegapunk's operation was shut down, and his
guinea pigs were thrown away like trash.
They did what they could to survive,
taking shelter in the third
laboratory, the only one
still intact.
There, they were protected from the poison
gas that contaminated the entire island.
Those who survived were paralyzed
from exposure to the gas,
which stole the use of their lower
bodies.
They lived on, without any
real hope for the future.
But then, a year later, everything
changed.
A kind master arrived on the island,
restoring the hope that had been
lost.
With his ability, he purified
the island of the toxic gas.
He also gave the prisoners who couldn't
walk the mechanical means to move.
More than that, he gave them purpose
by making them his loyal subordinates.
Kind master!
Master!
Merciful master!
I came to the island a year
after that, desperate and broken.
Two years have passed since my arrival.
Some toxic substances
remained in the air even then,
and breathing had left
me feeling nauseous.
I began to think I had no
more strength to carry on.
I had fought to survive,
but I was reaching the end.
But then I saw them, the men who had
lost the use of their legs just as I had.
And with them, the Master.
I owe everything to him.
His kindness saved my life
as it saved others before me.
Vega Punk and his experiments
stole my comrade's legs.
But then the master arrived.
A kind and generous savior.
And then a few months ago fate
brought us another surprise.
Trafalgar Law.
A warlord arrived on the island
and became our second savior.
Using his special ability.
He gave legs to those of us who couldn't
walk without mechanical assistance.
They were the legs of living animals.
We thought we would never walk again?
so we wept when our bodies were restored.
Oh, my God, that's the
most beautiful story ever!
You see, I told you Traffy was a good guy.
I'm not the only one whose life he saved.
How could Dr.
Vegapunk do something so horrible?
Well, I guess this explains the half-sheep
people, the ones back at the laboratory.
Centaurs and the Bird Woman.
It all makes sense now, except
the dragon. What's up with that?
Ah, yes.
Saw the dragon, did you?
That's just an artificial
creature Vegapunk
created to guard the island
from unwanted visitors.
It can adapt to any
environment imaginable.
I heard one of the world nobles
liked it and gave it a name.
I forgot what it was,
but run if you see it.
It's very aggressive.
I'm not worried.
We already ate it.
Now you know who's in charge on
the island and why we're here.
Nobody else dares to come near it now.
It belongs to the Master.
Punk hazard is the domain of our savior.
No, don't cry.
The Master continues his research
for the betterment of mankind.
To do so, he needs test subjects,
and each of you will have
the honor of becoming one.
Like it or not, you're his.
Hmm?
Is something the matter? Master!
Master, I can't breathe!
What kind of medicine is this?
Please, Master!
Master!
Please just let me out of here!
I need you to hang on a little longer.
Describe how you feel.
From the sound of it, there's
some nausea and coughing.
Does your head hurt as well? Yes.
It feels like it's going
to split open. Yes. Yes.
I see.
What?
It wasn't Vegapunk?
But he was in charge.
If Vegapunk didn't cause that
huge explosion, who did, Smokey?
The person who made the weapon
and accidentally set it off.
That was Caesar Clown.
He and Vegapunk worked together.
Caesar Clown was second in command here.
But because of his tendency
towards inhumane methods,
he and Vegapunk butted heads frequently.
Please, please, Master.
Please help me.
How are your eyes doing?
Are you seeing anything?
Strange
Too bad.
All right, that's enough.
Goodbye now
After the accident happened
Vegapunk was listed as
responsible because he was the
person in charge Of course,
it was a crime to develop
a chemical weapon of mass
destruction that could
take out an entire island.
When Caesar Clown's involvement came to
light after the explosion, he was arrested.
But, using his formidable ability,
he escaped from a prison ship.
And his location has been unknown since.
If my suspicions are correct and Caesar is
back here on this island
conducting experiments,
we have to stop him
before he does something.
even more horrible than before.
Giant snake.
Was this one another failure? Huh?
Failure, you say?
You really should watch your tongue.
My experiments are never failures,
not even what happened four years ago.
None of the useless idiots in the world
government know what they're talking
about a failed experiment i developed
a weapon that killed an entire island
how is that anything
but a success i proved
myself the most efficient
killer in the world
didn't i i meticulously
document each of my
victims until they draw their final breath
just you wait soon it
will be my day and they'll
know i'm the greatest
scientist to ever live
ROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROR
Thank you.